trading-pro.net 2019-07-07

# Privacy | TradingPRO

This Privacy Policy discloses the general privacy practices for the website – trading-pro.net. The owners of trading-pro.net, Trading Pro is committed to respecting your privacy rights when visiting this website. To protect your Personal Information, Trading Pro has created the guidelines outlined below when visiting trading-pro.net. Understanding that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving, any changes to this policy will be posted on this page, with an updated “effective date” posted at the end of this policy.

## Information Collected

We don’t collect any information when you browse this site, trading-pro.net, unless you make contact with us directly, register an account or purchase products from us.

If you purchase our products, we will keep a record of:

      * your order;
      * your name and lastname;
      * your phone number;
      * your street address;
      * company information (if a company);
      * your e-mail address;
      * relevant billing and account setup information;

But we don’t keep any payment instrument information, like your credit card number.

## IP Addresses

Trading Pro logs IP addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet when visiting trading-pro.net, for the purpose of identifying demand for our products, advertising and to determine site usage. Your IP address does not contain personal information about you.

## Use of Personal Information

We believe in protecting your privacy, and will not share Personal Information with any third parties. We may use your Personal Information, such as your e-mail address or mailing address, to contact you regarding products and/or services that may be of interest to you, to respond to an inquiry from you regarding the information that we have collected, or respond to your comments and suggestions.

## Links to Other Materials

Third party sites linked to and from the Site, trading-pro.net are not necessarily under instruction, agreement or control of Trading Pro, and therefore shall have no responsibilities or liabilities whatsoever for the content or privacy practices of any such linked site or any link or linking program at any time. Trading Pro does not necessarily endorse companies (or related products or services) to or from which the Site is linked. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to trading-pro.net, you do so entirely at your own risk.

## Security

Trading Pro maintains standard safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of the Personal Information that you provide when accessing trading-pro.net.

## Effective Date and Changes

This Privacy Policy is effective as of April 1st, 2019. Trading Pro reserves the right to modify the terms of this policy at any time and in our sole discretion, by posting a change notice to this page. Your continued use of the site, trading-pro.net following our posting of a change notice will constitute binding acceptance of those changes.

## How to Contact us

Should you have any questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [info@trading-pro.net](mailto:info@trading-pro.net).
